System Engineer · DevOps Engineer

ul. Pod Grapą 2 34-340 Jeleśnia

□ (+48) 531 255 368 | Sayupdate@gmail.com | Immichalmichulec

S	u	m	m	a	r	V

Starting from Level1 support I knew that OpenSource systems are future, so I immediately began to learn them. After 4 year yourney I realised that even complicated stuff might be understood in fixed time; thus there's no new thing that can scarry me from learning it. I want to learn and gain more experience in Linux, Automation and CI/CD pipelines.

Work Experience

Infomex Sp. z o.o.

Żywiec, Poland

System Engineer

Jan. 2019 - currently

- Maintenance of company OpenStack infrastructure (day to day tasks such as system upgrades, VM migrations, basic troubleshooting of locked VMs)
- Ansible automated environments for new customers
- PostgreSQL WAL streaming replica configuration

Infomex Sp. z o.o. Żywiec, Poland

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

Aug. 2018 - Jan. 2019

- Configuration of services for customers (Apache, Nginx, PHP-FPM)
- Setup of MySQL database clusters (Galera)
- · Basic tasks in OpenStack suite.

Infomex Sp. z o.o. Żywiec, Poland

JUNIOR SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

Dec. 2017 - Aug. 2018

- Provisioning of new systems for customers and configuration of software desired by customer.
- Configuring Zabbix monitoring for new systems also extending existing monitoring endpoints by additional checks
- Installation of new hardware in datacenter (HP Blade systems, HP EVA, HP 3PAR, HP Apollo)

Infomex Sp. z o.o. Żywiec, Poland

HELPDESK SPECIALIST

Jul. 2015 - Dec. 2017

- Level 1 helpdesk for company customers
- Monitoring of datacenter systems (including fire suppresion, cooling and IT systems performance)
- Resolving and debugging of simple system failures.

Education

Zespół Szkół Drzewnych i Leśnych

Żywiec, Poland

IT TECHNICAN

Sep. 2011 - Jul. 2015

Lan	gua	ges
-----	-----	-----

Polish *Native* **English** *professional working proficiency*

Hobbies

electronics biking books

JULY 29, 2019